dealshark.com 2007-02-18

# Privacy Policy

**Dealshark.com Privacy Policy**

**Your Privacy**  
Dealshark.com takes user privacy seriously and makes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. 

**Our Purpose**  
The Dealshark.com catalog represents Top Selling name brand items across most all product categories, and we offer Super Low Prices every day! 

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
In order to use certain portions of the Service, you may be asked for, or you may choose to provide, certain personally identifiable information (PII) such as name, email address, postal address, PayPal account and similar information. We will not collect PII from you while you use the Service unless you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collection such information. You authorize Dealshark.com to receive any account information from any affiliated merchant including, but not limited to, information regarding any purchase made by you through utilization of the Service, such as: the products ordered, the order number, the time and date of the purchase, the email address entered for the purchase. 

**Collection on Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
Dealshark.com does collect and track certain non-personally identifiable (non-PII) information, including but not limited to, user IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual. Our affiliate partners such as eBay, Amazon.com, and Shopping.com may set temporary cookies, for retaining your shopping cart and other technical purposes. “Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. We may use cookies to customize your use of the Service and for other purposes to improve your use of the Service, and may also use web beacons, web bugs, action tags and third party cookies. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to automatically retrieve PII from your computer without your knowledge. 

**User Agreement**  
Use of this Service is subject to the Dealshark.com User Agreement located at http://www.Dealshark.com/useragreement.html
